Marching boots lining up in the street.
Broken glass at a three minute speech.
Posters peel but the slogans stay new.
History repeats but the shade is still true.
Sneakers stained with the paint on the walls.
Truth gets lost in a parade of calls.
Blank devotion dressed up for the show.
How much flag do you need just to know?
You want red, white, and blue in your bed.
Tis a fact, let it cover your head.
Got the stars in your eye, fight on a crew.
Fifty shades of red, white, and blue.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
Wave the banners at the mirror every day.
Gradually just to the comfort on display.
Shaded green upon the rush of being right.
Raps so tight you can't see any light.
Disalimated every anthem played.
Worship power like the game you made.
You want red, white, and blue in your bed.
Just a flag, let it cover your head.
You got the stars in your eyes, fight on a crew.
Fifty shades of red, white, and blue.
[BLANK_AUDIO]